(window.webpackJsonp=window.webpackJsonp||[]).push([[0],{15:function(e){e.exports=[{category:"Entertainment%3A%20Video%20Games",type:"multiple",difficulty:"hard",question:"What%20was%20the%20name%20of%20the%20hero%20in%20the%2080s%20animated%20video%20game%20%27Dragon%27s%20Lair%27%3F",correct_answer:"Dirk%20the%20Daring",incorrect_answers:["Arthur","Sir%20Toby%20Belch","Guy%20of%20Gisbourne"]},{category:"Animals",type:"multiple",difficulty:"easy",question:"What%20is%20the%20scientific%20name%20for%20modern%20day%20humans%3F",correct_answer:"Homo%20Sapiens",incorrect_answers:["Homo%20Ergaster","Homo%20Erectus","Homo%20Neanderthalensis"]},{category:"Entertainment%3A%20Books",type:"multiple",difficulty:"hard",question:"What%20is%20Ron%20Weasley%27s%20middle%20name%3F",correct_answer:"Bilius",incorrect_answers:["Arthur","John","Dominic"]},{category:"Entertainment%3A%20Comics",type:"multiple",difficulty:"easy",question:"Who%20is%20the%20creator%20of%20the%20comic%20series%20%22The%20Walking%20Dead%22%3F",correct_answer:"Robert%20Kirkman",incorrect_answers:["Stan%20Lee","Malcolm%20Wheeler-Nicholson","Robert%20Crumb"]},{category:"Entertainment%3A%20Board%20Games",type:"multiple",difficulty:"medium",question:"At%20the%20start%20of%20a%20standard%20game%20of%20the%20Monopoly%2C%20if%20you%20throw%20a%20double%20six%2C%20which%20square%20would%20you%20land%20on%3F",correct_answer:"Electric%20Company",incorrect_answers:["Water%20Works","Chance","Community%20Chest"]},{category:"Geography",type:"multiple",difficulty:"easy",question:"What%20is%20the%20capital%20of%20Jamaica%3F",correct_answer:"Kingston",incorrect_answers:["Rio%20de%20Janeiro","Dar%20es%20Salaam","Kano"]},{category:"History",type:"multiple",difficulty:"medium",question:"When%20did%20Jamaica%20recieve%20its%20independence%20from%20England%3F%20",correct_answer:"1962",incorrect_answers:["1492","1963","1987"]},{category:"Animals",type:"boolean",difficulty:"easy",question:"Kangaroos%20keep%20food%20in%20their%20pouches%20next%20to%20their%20children.",correct_answer:"False",incorrect_answers:["True"]},{category:"General%20Knowledge",type:"multiple",difficulty:"medium",question:"In%202013%20how%20much%20money%20was%20lost%20by%20Nigerian%20scams%3F",correct_answer:"%2412.7%20Billion",incorrect_answers:["%2495%20Million","%24956%20Million","%242.7%20Billion"]},{category:"History",type:"multiple",difficulty:"medium",question:"How%20old%20was%20Lyndon%20B.%20Johnson%20when%20he%20assumed%20the%20role%20of%20President%20of%20the%20United%20States%3F",correct_answer:"55",incorrect_answers:["50","60","54"]},{category:"Entertainment%3A%20Video%20Games",type:"multiple",difficulty:"hard",question:"In%20World%20of%20Warcraft%20lore%2C%20who%20organized%20the%20creation%20of%20the%20Paladins%3F",correct_answer:"Alonsus%20Faol",incorrect_answers:["Uther%20the%20Lightbringer","Alexandros%20Mograine","Sargeras%2C%20The%20Daemon%20Lord"]},{category:"Entertainment%3A%20Video%20Games",type:"boolean",difficulty:"medium",question:"In%20the%20game%20%22Subnautica%22%2C%20a%20%22Cave%20Crawler%22%20will%20attack%20you.",correct_answer:"True",incorrect_answers:["False"]},{category:"Entertainment%3A%20Japanese%20Anime%20%26%20Manga",type:"multiple",difficulty:"medium",question:"What%20is%20the%20name%20of%20the%20device%20that%20allows%20for%20infinite%20energy%20in%20the%20anime%20%22Dimension%20W%22%3F",correct_answer:"Coils",incorrect_answers:["Wires","Collectors","Tesla"]},{category:"Entertainment%3A%20Video%20Games",type:"multiple",difficulty:"medium",question:"What%20is%20the%20name%20of%20Cream%20the%20Rabbit%27s%20mom%20in%20the%20%22Sonic%20the%20Hedgehog%22%20series%3F",correct_answer:"Vanilla",incorrect_answers:["Peach","Strawberry","Mint"]},{category:"History",type:"multiple",difficulty:"easy",question:"These%20two%20countries%20held%20a%20commonwealth%20from%20the%2016th%20to%2018th%20century.",correct_answer:"Poland%20and%20Lithuania",incorrect_answers:["Hutu%20and%20Rwanda","North%20Korea%20and%20South%20Korea","Bangladesh%20and%20Bhutan"]},{category:"Entertainment%3A%20Television",type:"multiple",difficulty:"hard",question:"Which%20of%20these%20voices%20wasn%27t%20a%20choice%20for%20the%20House%20AI%20in%20%22The%20Simpsons%20Treehouse%20of%20Horror%22%20short%2C%20House%20of%20Whacks%3F",correct_answer:"George%20Clooney",incorrect_answers:["Matthew%20Perry","Dennis%20Miller","Pierce%20Brosnan"]},{category:"Entertainment%3A%20Music",type:"multiple",difficulty:"medium",question:"From%20which%20album%20is%20the%20Gorillaz%20song%2C%20%22On%20Melancholy%20Hill%22%20featured%20in%3F",correct_answer:"Plastic%20Beach",incorrect_answers:["Demon%20Days","Humanz","The%20Fall"]},{category:"General%20Knowledge",type:"boolean",difficulty:"easy",question:"Scotland%20voted%20to%20become%20an%20independent%20country%20during%20the%20referendum%20from%20September%202014.",correct_answer:"False",incorrect_answers:["True"]},{category:"Entertainment%3A%20Video%20Games",type:"multiple",difficulty:"medium",question:"In%20Left%204%20Dead%2C%20which%20campaign%20has%20the%20protagonists%20going%20through%20a%20subway%20in%20order%20to%20reach%20a%20hospital%20for%20evacuation%3F",correct_answer:"No%20Mercy",incorrect_answers:["Subway%20Sprint","Hospital%20Havoc","Blood%20Harvest"]},{category:"History",type:"multiple",difficulty:"hard",question:"What%20was%20the%20last%20colony%20the%20UK%20ceded%20marking%20the%20end%20of%20the%20British%20Empire%3F",correct_answer:"Hong%20Kong",incorrect_answers:["India","Australia","Ireland"]}]},19:function(e,t,n){e.exports=n(27)},24:function(e,t,n){},25:function(e,t,n){},27:function(e,t,n){"use strict";n.r(t);var a=n(0),r=n.n(a),o=n(18),c=n.n(o),i=(n(24),n(25),n(16)),s=n(1);function l(){var e=Object(s.m)();return r.a.createElement("div",{className:"background"},r.a.createElement("div",{className:"welcome"},r.a.createElement("h1",null,"Welcome to this quiz"),r.a.createElement("h3",null,"You have 20 questions to answer in 10 minutes. Good luck!"),r.a.createElement("button",{className:"startButton",type:"button",onClick:function(){return e("/start")}},"Take quiz")))}var u=n(3),m=function(e){var t=e.questionNumber,n=e.totalNumOfQuestions,a=t/n*100;return r.a.createElement("div",{className:"progress"},r.a.createElement("div",{className:"progress-bar questionNumber",role:"progressbar","aria-valuemin":"0","aria-valuemax":n.toString(),style:{width:"".concat(a,"%")}}))},d=n(5),h=function(e){var t=e.numOfQuestionsAnswered,n=e.numOfCorrectAnswers,a=e.numOfWrongAnswers,o=e.totalNumOfQuestions,c=Math.floor(n/o*100),i=0===t?0:Math.ceil((n/t*100).toFixed(2)),s=Math.floor((o-a)/o*100);return r.a.createElement("div",{className:"tracker","data-testid":"1"},r.a.createElement("p",{className:"score"},r.a.createElement("span",{"data-testid":"score"},"Score: ".concat(i,"%")),r.a.createElement("span",null,"Max Score: ".concat(s,"%"))),r.a.createElement("div",{className:"progress"},r.a.createElement("div",{className:"progress-bar leastPossibleScore",role:"progressbar",style:{width:"".concat(c,"%")}}),r.a.createElement("div",{className:"progress-bar currentScore",role:"progressbar",style:{width:"".concat(i-c,"%")}}," "),r.a.createElement("div",{className:"progress-bar  highestPossibleScore",role:"progressbar",style:{width:"".concat(s-i,"%")}})))};function f(e){var t=e.calculatedScoreAfterElapsedTime,n=r.a.useState(600),a=Object(u.a)(n,2),o=a[0],c=a[1],i=r.a.useState(!0),s=Object(u.a)(i,2),l=s[0],m=s[1],d=r.a.useState(!1),h=Object(u.a)(d,2),f=h[0],y=h[1];r.a.useEffect(function(){var e;return l?e=setInterval(function(){c(function(e){return e-1})},1e3):clearInterval(e),function(){return clearInterval(e)}},[l]),r.a.useEffect(function(){0===o&&l&&(m(!1),y(!0),t())},[o,l,t]);var w=String(o%60).padStart(2,0),p=String(Math.floor(o/60)).padStart(2,0);return r.a.createElement("div",{className:"timer"},r.a.createElement("h2",null,f?r.a.createElement("span",null,"Time's Up"):r.a.createElement("span",null,p,":",w," ")))}var y=function(e){var t,n=e.questionNumber,o=e.totalNumOfQuestions,c=e.selectedQuestion,i=e.correctAnswerIndex,s=e.showNextQuestion,l=Object(a.useState)(null),m=Object(u.a)(l,2),y=m[0],w=m[1],p=Object(a.useState)(!1),g=Object(u.a)(p,2),b=g[0],E=g[1],v=Object(a.useState)(0),S=Object(u.a)(v,2),_=S[0],N=S[1],A=Object(a.useState)(0),q=Object(u.a)(A,2),O=q[0],C=q[1],k=Object(a.useState)(0),W=Object(u.a)(k,2),F=W[0],j=W[1],H=Object(a.useRef)(),M=Object(a.useState)(!1),I=Object(u.a)(M,2),B=I[0],T=I[1];Object(a.useEffect)(function(){if(B){document.querySelectorAll(".button").forEach(function(e){e.disabled=!0});var e=o-_;N(20),j(function(t){return t+e}),E(!1)}},[B,_,o]),null===y&&(t=""),!0===y&&(t="Correct!"),!1===y&&(t="Sorry!");var x=decodeURIComponent(c.category),G=decodeURIComponent(c.question),Q=function(e,t,n,a,r){e===t?(w(!0),C(function(e){return e+1})):(w(!1),j(function(e){return e+1}),H.current.classList.add("correctAnswer")),N(function(e){return e+1}),n.target.classList.add("clicked"),E(a!==r),document.querySelectorAll(".button").forEach(function(e){e.disabled=!0})};return r.a.createElement("div",{className:"container "},r.a.createElement("h2",null,"Question ".concat(n," of ").concat(o)),r.a.createElement("h5",null,x),r.a.createElement("h6",null,function(e){var t,n=[];"hard"===e&&(t=3),"medium"===e&&(t=2),"easy"===e&&(t=1);for(var a=0;a<t;a++)n.push(r.a.createElement("i",{key:a,className:"bi bi-star-fill"}));return n}(c.difficulty)),r.a.createElement("h4",null,G),r.a.createElement("div",{className:"options"},function(){var e=decodeURIComponent(c.correct_answer),t=c.incorrect_answers.map(function(t){var a=decodeURIComponent(t);return r.a.createElement("button",{onClick:function(t){return Q(a,e,t,n,o)},className:"button"},a)}),a=Object(d.a)(t);return a.splice(i,0,r.a.createElement("button",{ref:H,onClick:function(t){return Q(e,e,t,n,o)},className:"button"},e)),a}()),r.a.createElement("div",{className:"correct text-center"},r.a.createElement("h2",{className:"result","data-testid":"correct"},t),b&&r.a.createElement("button",{onClick:function(){s(),w(null),document.querySelectorAll(".button").forEach(function(e){e.disabled=!1}),E(!1),H.current.classList.remove("correctAnswer"),document.querySelector(".clicked").classList.remove("clicked")},className:"next"},"Next question")),r.a.createElement(h,{numOfQuestionsAnswered:_,numOfCorrectAnswers:O,numOfWrongAnswers:F,totalNumOfQuestions:o}),r.a.createElement(f,{calculatedScoreAfterElapsedTime:function(){T(!0)}}))},w=n(15);var p=function(){var e=Object(a.useState)(1),t=Object(u.a)(e,2),n=t[0],o=t[1],c=Math.floor(4*Math.random());return r.a.createElement("div",null,r.a.createElement(m,{questionNumber:n,totalNumOfQuestions:w.length}),r.a.createElement(y,{selectedQuestion:w[n-1],totalNumOfQuestions:w.length,questionNumber:n,correctAnswerIndex:c,showNextQuestion:function(){o(function(e){return e+1})}}))};Boolean("localhost"===window.location.hostname||"[::1]"===window.location.hostname||window.location.hostname.match(/^127(?:\.(?:25[0-5]|2[0-4][0-9]|[01]?[0-9][0-9]?)){3}$/));c.a.render(r.a.createElement(function(){return r.a.createElement("div",null,r.a.createElement(i.a,null,r.a.createElement(s.c,null,r.a.createElement(s.a,{path:"/",element:r.a.createElement(l,null)}),r.a.createElement(s.a,{path:"/start",element:r.a.createElement(p,null)}))))},null),document.getElementById("root")),"serviceWorker"in navigator&&navigator.serviceWorker.ready.then(function(e){e.unregister()})}},[[19,1,2]]]);
//# sourceMappingURL=main.9e2729a6.chunk.js.map